Guide to the Open University Records
University of Houston Libraries
- Classroom Material
  - The City in Newly Developing Countries Readings on Urbanism and Urbanization, Editor - Gerald Breese (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - The Modern Metropolis, Selected Essays by Hans Blumenfeld, Its Origins, Growth, Characteristics, and Planning, Edited by Paul D. Spreiregen (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Audio/Video Tapes
  This series includes 5 boxes of audio and video teaching aids meant to be used both inside and outside the classroom. The audio tapes include cassettes and records for Art, Social Science, and Math/ Technology classes. There are 25 video tapes organized by title, which include The Age of Revolution, The Third Testament, and Humanities. This series also includes one promotional video done by the BBC.
  - A303 Audio Tapes 1-16 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - D101 Audio Tapes 1-28 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - MDT 241 Audio Tapes 1-8 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - DT201 Flexi-Discs (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Urban Development DT 201 Disc 1 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Urban Development DT 201 Disc 2 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - DT201 Flexi-Discs, Disc 1,2, 3-10 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - A202 Audio Tapes 1-34 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Roots - A Second Looks Cassettes 1-13 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Anyone For Tennyson Cassettes 1-4 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Crime and Justice Audio Aids 15-8, 13-15 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Beethoven Cassette (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Cassette D201 21 Chicago - Voluntary Associations (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - The Age of Revolutions - Thirteen Colonies, The Terror (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - The Age of Revolutions - The Machine in the English Cotton Industry, Looking at Napoleon (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - The Age of Revolutions - #1 Wordsworth, #2 Kant and Causality (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - The Age of Revolutions - Daumer and his Robert Macaire, Slave Trade (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Age of Revolution - #1 Immanual Kant, #2 Humphry Davy (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - The Age of Revolutions - Ingres, Super Being (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - The Age of Revolutions - Romantic Primitivism (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - The Third Testament - Blake (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - The Third Testament - Kierkegaard (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - The Third Testament - Pascal (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - The Third Testament - Tolstoy (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Open University Explanation Film by the BBC (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Humanities - Leda and The Swan, Victorian Cast Iron (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Humanities - Clouds - Aristophanes, Socrates - A Discussion (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - The Third Testament - St. Augustine, Pascal (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - The Third Testament (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Humanities and Fine Arts Foundations I - “Action - A Philosophical Discussion”, Isambard Kingdom Brunel (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Humanities Reading a Poem - Mendelssohn (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Humanities - Glasgow - The Industrial City, The Image of the Cloud (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Humanities - Isambard Kingdom Brunel, Music I (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Humanities - Signs of the Times, Instruments of the Orchestra (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Humanities - What is Civilization?, Religious Responses (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Humanities - View of the Renaissance, Art and the Artifact (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Humanities - The Necessity of History, “Vasaris Life of Donattlo” (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Humanities - Perception - A Philosophical Discussion, Logical Poems (Box 18, Folder 9)